<resources>
    <string name="app_name">1601 Assignment Quiz</string>
    <string name="yes_button_label">Yes</string>
    <string name="no_button_label">No</string>

    <string name="previous_button_label">Previous</string>
    <string name="submit_button_label">Submit</string>
    <string name="next_button_label">Next</string>

    <string name="display_score_toast">%1$s You scored %2$d out of %3$d%4$s</string>
    <string name="prefix_pass">Nice!</string>
    <string name="prefix_fail">Good try!</string>
    <string name="punctuation_pass">!</string>
    <string name="punctuation_fail">.</string>


    <string name="question1">
        1. Which of the following statements are NOT true regarding Android Studio?
        [Android Studio 2.3 is the latest stable release]
        Android Studio is built specifically for Android development|
        Android Studio 2.3 is the latest stable release|
        Android Studio is an IDE (Integrated Development Environment)|
        Android Studio is built on IntelliJ software|
        Android Studio can be run on Windows, Mac, and Linux|
    </string>
    <string name="question2">
        2. Which of the following languages are markup languages?
        [XML]
        XML|
        Java|
        Kotlin|
        Python|
        Scratch|
    </string>
    <string name="question3">
        3. Which categories of products can Android apps be developed for?
        [All of the above]
        Phones and Tablets|
        Watches|
        TVs|
        Car Systems|
        All of the above|
    </string>
    <string name="question4">
        4. When coding an Android program, in which location should you put the source of a
        paragraph of text that is displayed within the app?
        [As a resource inside the strings.xml file]
        In its own Java class|
        In its own Enum|
        In the MainActivity class as a constant|
        As a Gradle Script inside the build.gradle file|
        As a resource inside the strings.xml file|
    </string>
    <string name="question5">
        5. Which of the following demonstrate good naming conventions for XML and Java file names?
        [activity_main.xml and MainActivity.java]
        MainActivity.xml and MainActivity.java|
        activity_main.xml and activity_main.java|
        main_activity.xml and main_activity.java|
        activity_main.xml and MainActivity.java|
        main_activity.xml and MainActivity.java|
    </string>
    <string name="question6">
        6. Which of the following is the latest Android API level as of January 2019?
        [28]
        1|
        8|
        20|
        28|
        34|
    </string>
    <string name="question7">
        7. Which methods in the activity lifecycle are automatically called when the device screen
        is rotated?
        [onPause, onStop, onDestroy, onCreate, onStart, onResume]
        No methods are automatically called|
        onCreate|
        onPause, onResume|
        onPause, onStop, onStart, onResume|
        onPause, onStop, onDestroy, onCreate, onStart, onResume|
    </string>
    <string name="question8">
        8. What is the difference between an argument and a parameter?
        [Parameters are part of a method definition, while arguments are the actual instances
        that are passed into the method]
        They mean the same thing|
        Arguments only for the main method, parameters are for all other methods|
        Parameters are part of a method definition, while arguments are the actual instances
        that are passed into the method|
        Arguments are part of a method definition, while parameters are the actual instances
        that are passed into the method|
        Arguments are arrays, while parameters are single objects|
    </string>
    <string name="question9">
        9. Which of the following statements are NOT true regarding resource IDs?
        [All resources need IDs attached to them in order to be referenced]
        Resource IDs can be added to XML tags explicitly|
        All resources need IDs attached to them in order to be referenced|
        IDs can be accessed from Java programs using R.id|
        XML resource files can reference other XML resources by ID|
        Spaces and some symbols are not allowed in a resource ID|
    </string>
    <string name="question10">
        10. What should be the first line of code in a onCreate method in MainActivity?
        (Assume savedInstanceState is an object of the Bundle class)
        [super.onCreate(savedInstanceState);]
        It does not matter|
        onCreate();|
        onCreate(savedInstanceState);|
        super.onCreate();|
        super.onCreate(savedInstanceState);|
    </string>
</resources>
